<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ryder Davis</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ryder Davis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello! Welcome to my first blog post!
In this post I’m going to talk a little bit about regular expressions. With regular expressions, you can find certain pieces within a chunk of code. To make it easier, a cheat sheet will be below.
By using these special symbols, you can decide what you want to pick out. We’re going to find all occurences, so we’ll need to import re, then use the template re.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bio</title>
      <link>/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bio/</guid>
      <description>About Me   Biography
  Here is my terrible high school resume that is a treat to read.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biography</title>
      <link>/biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/biography/</guid>
      <description>My name is Ryder Davis. I was born in San Antonio, and I moved to Austin when I was 5, and I have been here since. I graduated from Rouse High School and am currently attending the University of Texas at Austin. I enjoy watching and playing the majority of sports. In high school, I played golf and ultimate frisbee, two compldtely different sports. I also enjoy video games and listening to music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Ryder Davis rkd473 The dataset I selected was one from the carData package called Arrests, which is about information regarding marijuana arrests. The variables are released, colour (race), year, age, sex, employed (Y/N), citizen (Y/N), and checks. Most of these are intuitive, and the ones that aren’t are released, which is if the arrestee was released with a summons, and checks, which is the number of police data bases the arrestee’s name was on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project1</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Ryder Davis rkd473 The datasets I have chosen both are about professional golf statistics. I played golf for my high school, so I have a deeper than average understanding of the game. Seeing a professional play just amazes me as how good they are. I don’t think many people realize how precise and consistent you have to be to even play in a pro tournament. I expect that the majority of the statistics will be very close among all the players because winning in golf at that level comes down to whether or not you had a good day/week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>